Guide to the Edison Price Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Slides, Negatives, and Photographs, 1953–1996; Series VI
  - Negatives
    - Lighting table and repeat table, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Lighting fixtures, Circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Loring EKD tests, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, New York, 1993–1995 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Off camera flash mockups, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Parhoop and Parscoop, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Parhoop final, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Personal photographs, Undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Plus X, ID11, M7, Undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Sketch, Undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - View of office through fish eye lense, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Photographs, fixtures and products
    - Autotrack, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Barbizon-Plaza Hotel chandelier
      - Elevator, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Elevator, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Hub, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Light test, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Early lighting fixtures, Circa 1950s (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Eminent Technology Tonearm 2, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Fixture DF 12, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Flourescent lighting fixtures, Circa 1970s (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Giraffe lamp, Circa 1950s (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Johnson Kelly lamp, Circa 1960s (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Loring point obstruction light, Perrin and Denver, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Luminaire, Circa 1980s (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Off camera flash mock-up, Circa 1980s (Box 30, Folder 12-13)
    - Off camera flash mock-up, final, Circa 1980s (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Oxford markup, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Par 56 and Parhoop, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Parhoop, final, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Parscoop, Circa 1980s (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Product No. 5147, Circa 1950s (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Sheetrock and Swidlux test, 1993 October 26 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Skyhook television lighting fixture, Circa 1950s (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Tools, Circa 1970s (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Wall mount and Parhoop, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Wall mount and Parhoop, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, projects and people
    - 110 Green Street, New York, New York, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - A.G. Becker, pendant Visionair and Uminair, Chicago, Illinois, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Albright Knox Gallery, Buffalo, New York, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Amon Carter Museum, Fort Worth, Texas, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Associated Metals and Minerals, Darklite and Uminair, New York, New York, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Baltmore Museum, Baltimore, Maryland, 1993–1994 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New Haven, Connecticut, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Brandywine River Museum, Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Chemical Bank, Visionair, Detroit, Michigan, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Civic Center, courtroom, Chicago, Illinois, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Chicopee, Uminair, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Citi Bank, high specular Visionair, New York, New York, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Cleo Rogers Memorial Library, Columbus, Indiana, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art Addition, Cleveland, Ohio, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Information Center, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Columbia Fairchild Labs, pendant Visionair, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Combustion Engineering, Stamford, Connecticut, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Combustion Engineering, Stamford, Connecticut
      - Photograph, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Negative, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Commercial Metals Company, 14' Desklite, Visionair, A19WW, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Denver Art Museum, Denver, Colorado, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Design sketch, Undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Donald C. Thomas office, Sylvania Lighting, GTE Products Corporation, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Ebasco, Visionair, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Edison Price and chandelier hub, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Edison Price, portraits, Circa 1960s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Edison Price, Inc., employees, Circa 1970s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Ezra Stoller Prints, 1960–1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Fenimore Art Museum, Cooperstown, New York, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - First City National Bank, Houston, Texas, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Four Seasons Restaurant, Seagram Building, New York, New York, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Four Seasons Restaurant, Seagram Building, New York, New York, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Georgia Pacific, Atlanta, Georgia, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Grey Advertising, Visionair, New York, New York, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Haj Terminal, Saudi Arabia, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Haj Terminal, Saudi Arabia, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Hartford Life Insurance Building, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Holy Angels Church, Chicago, Illinois, 1989–1991 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Houston Lighting and Power Company, Houston, Texas, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Houston Post, Houston, Texas, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), New York City Headquarters, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), Visionair and gallery, New York, New York, Circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - J.M. Huber, Edison, New Jersey, Circa 1980s (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - J. Paul Getty Center, Los Angeles, California, 1991 October 9 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Loring Offices, Visionair, New York, New York, Circa 1980s (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Kalamazoo Institute of Art, Kalamazoo, Michigan, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Kimbell Art Museum, Fort Worth, Texas, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Knoll Associates Chicago Showroom, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Le Grand Louvre, Paris, France, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lincoln Center Library and Museum of the Performing Arts, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln Center, Vivian Beaumont Theater, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - List of photographs and negatives of projects, Undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Marlborough-Gerson Gallery, New York, New York, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, New York
      - Unused negatives and prints, 1993–1995 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Oversize photographs, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Midway Electrical, Nulux warehouse, Brooklyn, New York, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Midway Electrical, Nulux warehouse, Brooklyn, New York, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Museum of Modern Art, Tensegrity Mast installation, New York, New York, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Morgan Guarantee, 20 Pine Street, Visionair, New York, New York, Circa 1980s (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Munson-Williams-Proctor Museum, Utica, New York, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Museum conservation vendors, Circa 1990s (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Museum of Modern Art, Tensegrity Mast, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - National Airlines Terminal, John F. Kennedy Airport, New York, New York, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - National Gallery, Washington, District of Columbia, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - New York Savings Bank, New York, New York, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Nulux, holiday party, 1991 December 22 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Pan-Am Terminal, John F. Kennedy Airport, New York, New York, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Philip Johnson, Circa 1960s (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Photograph album of projects completed, Circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 9-10)
    - Place Ville Marie, Montreal, Quebec, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Presentation boards, Circa 1980s (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1960s (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1960s (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1980s (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1980s (Box 35, Folder 12-13)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1980s (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Saidye Bronfman Cultural Center, Young Men's, Young Women's Hebrew Association (YM - YWHA), Montreal, Quebec, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Seagram Building lobby, New York, New York, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill (SOM), New York, Visionair and continuous rows, Circa 1980s (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, Houston, Texas, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Upjohn Executive Headquarters building, Kalamazoo, Michigan, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Warner Lambert, Visionair, computer room, Circa 1980s (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Whitney Museum of Art, New York, New York, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Personal and Family Records, 1910–1986; Series VII
  This series consists of photographs and personal records attributed to Edison Price and his parents, William Price and Alice Price.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by family member name. Folders within each family member grouping are arranged alphabetically.
  - Alice Price
    - Photographs, 1910, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Includes label indicating photographs are of Clara Avery, Price's birth name.
  - Edison Price
    - Career and family history timeline, Undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
      This timeline was collected and written by Delia Price, daughter of Edison Price.
    - Correspondence, 1976–1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Passport, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, 1946, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - General Price family records
    - Display Stage Lighting Co. Inc., calendar, 1918 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Vintage cars, photographs and negatives, 1986 February (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - William Price
    - Death notice, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Elks dues card, 1919 October 23 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, 1916, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)